https://mosys.com/company/privacy-policy/

VIRTUAL ACCELERATOR ENGINES
Packet Classification for Anti-Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) Engines – Combining AI/ML with ACL Lookups
OTHER
In Memory Functions – Fixed Functions (BURST/RMW)
PHE – RISC Core Instruction Set
GigaChip Interface (IP)
Stellar Virtual Accelerator Engines
Chiplet Interconnect – Parallel or Serial?
VIRTUAL ACCELERATOR ENGINES
Packet Classification for Anti-Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) Engines – Combining AI/ML with ACL Lookups
OTHER
In Memory Functions – Fixed Functions (BURST/RMW)
PHE – RISC Core Instruction Set
GigaChip Interface (IP)
Stellar Virtual Accelerator Engines
Chiplet Interconnect – Parallel or Serial?
Privacy Policy
THIS PRIVACY POLICY SETS FORTH THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS GOVERNING OUR COLLECTION, USE AND MAINTENANCE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE WHEN VISITING THE MOSYS, INC. (“MOSYS”) WEBSITE (“WEBSITE”). IT DOES NOT APPLY TO MOSYS’S OFFLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE AND MAINTENANCE PRACTICES. BY ACCESSING, BROWSING AND/OR USING THE WEBSITE, YOU ARE DEEMED TO ACCEPT THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, AS THEY MAY BE AMENDED FROM TIME TO TIME. IF YOU DO NOT WISH TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT ACCESS, BROWSE OR USE THE WEBSITE. WHAT INFORMATION IS COLLECTED FROM USERS. We receive and log certain types of information whenever you visit www.mosys.com. For example, we automatically receive information about your IP address, Internet browser and operating system. Please note, there are a number of companies that offer utilities designed to help you visit websites anonymously in the event you wish to visit our website without providing such information. Additionally, MoSys.com requires users to submit the personal information identified to access selected information such as the technical specifications of our various products. In addition, if you send us an e-mail, request information from us or apply for a position at MoSys, the information contained in those communications is collected.
HOW DOES MOSYS USE THE COLLECTED INFORMATION
The information we track and log in connection with your session(s) is used internally to analyze trends, administer the site, help diagnose problems with our servers, track users’ movements in the aggregate, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use and generally to improve our site and the services we offer you. In addition, we may use the information obtained to inform you about new products and promotions via electronic mail. In addition, we use the information you provide in communicating with us to respond to your requests. Finally, we use the information you provide in applying for positions at MoSys to evaluate your qualifications for the position.
YOUR OPT OUT RIGHT
As indicated above, MoSys may use certain information you provide to us to send you information and materials that we think may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to receive any further information or materials from us, such as e-mails or newsletters, you have the right to opt out of the receipt of such materials. To opt out from receiving such materials, you must check the appropriate box provided at the time you are requested to provide personal information. If, at a later time, you wish to express or change your preference, you may do so by contacting us at the address indicated below.
WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW DOES MOSYS.COM USE THEM
Please note that MoSys.com uses “cookies” in the collection of user data. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Only the information that you provide to us is included in the cookie, and cookies cannot take any additional information from your hard drive. By using cookies, the MoSys website is able to recognize you and your preferences when you revisit the website. Cookies are placed on your browser for your convenience.
HOW TO SET YOUR BROWSER TO ACCEPT COOKIES
If you’re using Internet Explorer, go to the View menu and select Internet Options. Within the Internet Options window, select the Advanced tab at the top right, scroll down until you see a selection titled “Cookies” and check the “Always accept cookies” box.If you’re using Netscape Navigator, go to the Options menu and select Network Preferences. Within the Network Preferences window, select the Protocols tab. There is a heading titled “Show an Alert Before” and a check box next to a selection titled “Accepting a Cookie.” If this is not checked, you will automatically accept cookies without being warned by your browser.
WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE USER INFORMATION
Except as mentioned below, MoSys will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your explicit permission. We may merge personal information about you into group data, which may then be shared on an aggregate basis with our investors, partners or licensees, but such information will not reveal your individual identity and no one will be able to identify or contact you on the basis of that information. MoSys may use personal information collected or in its possession to contact users in connection with their inappropriate use of the Website, noncompliance with the Terms of Use, or in connection with a complaint filed about their use of one of the Website by another user. MoSys also may disclose your personal information to another party, such as law enforcement officials, to comply with legal requirements, court orders, government or law enforcement agency requests, to protect or defend MoSys, or where we perceive an immediate danger of death or serious physical injury to someone as a result of activity on the Website. Our disclosures may occur under circumstances where we may not be authorized to advise you of such action.
LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES
This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on the Website. The Website may contain links to other web sites. You may be asked by these web sites to provide personal information or to release information you may have provided on our Website. You are never required to release this information, and whether you do is optional and strictly up to you. MoSys has no control or influence over the privacy practices of these other web sites. This would also apply to these web sites’ use of cookies and other electronically collected data. If you release your personal information to a third party web site visited through our Website, MoSys is not be responsible for any actions of such third party web site, nor any adverse consequences that may result from your interaction with such third party web site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every web site they visit.
DATA CORRECTION AND DATA REMOVAL
If you wish to update or correct any of the personal data you’ve provided to MoSys, or to change your user permission status so as not to receive any information or material from MoSys, you may do so by submitting the following online form: Contact Us
OUR SECURITY PRECAUTIONS
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we strive to protect your personal information, MoSys cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit. All such information is provided to us at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we make all commercially reasonable efforts to ensure its security on our systems.
USE OF WWW.MOSYS.COM BY CHILDREN
While www.mosys.com products, ad campaigns and marketing materials may be viewed by children, the website is not directed to children. In accordance with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), MoSys will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without parental consent. When we do receive information (with parental consent) from users under the age of 13, we will not share their personally identifiable information with third parties, regardless of their stated preference given at registration.
CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We will notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy. If we make material changes in our Privacy Policy that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on the Website notifying users of the change. If we propose to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email, and you will have a choice as to whether we may use your information in this different manner. However, if your account has been deleted or activated, you will not be contacted, but your personal information will not be used in this new manner.
COMPLAINTS
If you do not believe that your personal information has been handled in a manner consistent with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please contact:
MoSys, Inc.2309 Bering DriveSan Jose, CA 95131
Lets stay connected.
MoSys’ innovative Memory ICs improve system speed and performance while eliminating data throughput and access bottlenecks on line cards and systems with aggregate rates above 100Gbps.
Products
Quazar Family
Blazar Family
Stellar Family
Line Speed Family
Development Kits
Applications
Design Support
© 2020 MoSys, Inc.
